publicflash.com 2018-01-05

# PublicFlash.com - Nude Where Not Allowed -

Any personal information provided to or gathered by this site is controlled by PublicFlash.com 

As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future. If such changes are not substantial in amount or in limiting your privacy rights, such changes will be posted here with an updated effective date. All substantial changes- both in amount and in limiting your privacy rights- will be emailed to you prior to becoming effective. 

_Adults Only Service_

**THIS IS AN ADULTS ONLY SERVICE.** We will suspend or terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Sites; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person. 

_What We Collect_

During sign up we require that you provide us with certain information which may include Account Data (i.e., your name, physical address, email address, phone number, username, and password) and "Demographic Information". Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history. Please note that all financial data you may submit in connection with any purchase will be submitted directly to the third party payment processor which will be processing your purchase. The use of such data will be subject to such payment processor's own privacy policy which you will need to review separate and apart from this Policy before making any purchase. 

_How We Use the Information We Collect_

Account Data will be used to maintain and administer your account. We may use "cookies" and Demographic Information to better your experience on the Site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information. Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties for the purpose of website administration and optimization including, without limitation, analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Sites. 

_You Are Responsible For Information You Provide to Third Parties_

We are not responsible for the use of any information you may choose to share with third parties through our Site. You should treat the Site and service as a public forum and not share anything that you would not want to share with the public generally. 

_Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety_

Although your name, physical address, phone number and email address are generally considered confidential, all information you provide to us may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system. In the event that we believe that your use of the Site or service may constitute a violation of any law, we reserve the right to proactively provide all information relating to your account, including the Account Data, to law enforcement and any and all other agencies we may deem appropriate. 

_Emails From Us and use of Your Email Address_

Your email address will be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your subscription to the Sites. We may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive email from us. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us please unsubscribe by emailing us at webmaster[at]publicflash[dot]com. We reserve the right to share your email address with third parties for the purposes of such third parties advertising websites and services you may be interested in to you. Our emails will fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and we will require that any third party with whom we share your email address agrees to comply with CAN-SPAM. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent. Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Sites. 

_Advertisements_

We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or "action tags" to measure advertising effectiveness on an "anonymous basis". Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Sites. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms of use or privacy policies for such advertisers' websites, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Sites on such advertisers' website(s). 

Changes to the Privacy Policy 

We may change this privacy policy at any time. Any and all changes to this Policy will be posted here with an updated effective date. In the event that any changes are substantial and/or substantially limit your privacy rights, we will provide you with notice to the email address you have provided to us. 

Changes in the Ownership of the Sites 

The Sites may have the occasion to buy or sell assets including, by way of example only, through a merger, dissolution, and/or transfer of ownership. Depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us with third parties as may be necessary or appropriate to initiate, investigate, and/or complete any such transaction(s).
